Guide to the Lydia Coye Holcomb family papers, 1796-1959
Holcomb, Lydia Coye family papers, 1796-1959
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lydia Coye Holcomb family papers, 1796-1959.
3488
Lydia Coye Holcomb.
.9 cubic ft.
Correspondence, diaries, newspaper clippings, a genealogical register, a family ledger, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, diaries, and other papers of the Holcomb family.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Family news and details of their health, economic and social status, and migrations are discussed in letters to Lydia Lavern Brown Coye Holcomb and to her son, Elmer N. Coye, in Ontario County, New York, from Alice Sabina Brown Morgan, Sarah Ann Brown Olmstead, and Vesta A. Olmstead, California; Hersalora Catherine Brown Stephenson, Illinois; Juliet A. Brown, Sanford Brown, Sarah A. Brown, and Emma A. Brown, Hungerford, Iowa; Avery Brown, Elmera Brown Dickinson and Maryett Brown Matteson, Kansas; Otis Gilbert Brown, South Dakota; Amelia Brown, Byron Brown, and Carrie A. Brown, Wisconsin; and L. DeWitt Brown and S. Alcesta Easton. Also includes later correspondence among the following Coye and Holcomb family members: Mrs. Herbert Coye, William Coye, Winifred Coye, Adelbert Holcomb, Alice Roderick Holcomb, Elva Wilson, and Howard Wilson; business correspondence relating to the Holcomb & Coye farm and apiary; Nathan H. Coye's account books (1845-1859); Avery Brown's letter journals sent from Wisconsin to his family in Ontario County (1854); Lydia Coye Holcomb's diaries (1867, 1883, 1888-1896); Elmer N. Coye's diaries (1869, 1890); newspaper clippings (in part, photocopies); Brown family genealogical register; Coye family ledger, 1796-1849; and material related to the Wilson family, 1909-1959.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Holcomb, Lydia Coye.; Brown family.; Brown, Amelia.; Brown, Avery.; Brown, Byron.; Brown, Carrie A.; Brown, Emma A.; Brown, Juliet A.; Brown, L. DeWitt.; Brown, Otis Gilbert.; Brown, Sanford.; Brown, Sarah A.; Coye family.; Coye, Elmer N.; Coye, Elmer N.; Coye, Mrs. Herbert.; Coye, Nathan H.; Coye, William.; Coye, Winifred.; Dickinson, Elmera Brown.; Easton, S. Alcesta.; Holcomb family.; Holcomb, Adelbert.; Holcomb, Alice.; Holcomb, Ida.; Holcomb, James.; Holcomb, L. Laverna.; Matteson, Maryett Brown.; Morgan, Alice Sabina Brown.; Olmstead, Sarah Ann Brown.; Olmstead, Vesta A.; Stephenson, Hersalora Catherine Brown.; Wilson family.; Wilson, Elva.; Wilson, Howard.; Holcomb & Coye Farm.
Subjects:
Agriculture.
Places:
Ontario County (N.Y.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1849-1853 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1854-1856 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1857 (Jan.-Apr.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1857 (May-Dec.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1858 (Jan.-July) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1858 (Aug.-Dec.) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1859 (Jan.-May) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1859 (June-Dec.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1861-1862 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1864-1866 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1867-1869 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1870-1875 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1877-1879 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1880-1881 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1882-1886 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1887-1888 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1890-1893 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1894-1896 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1897, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1909-1916, 1941-1942, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Loose papers from diaries (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Coye Family Ledger (photocopy), 1796-1849 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- New Testament, from Lydia Laverna Brown to Sarah Ann Brown, 1842 (Box 3)
- Nathan Coye: account with Field & Little, 1845-1857 (Box 3)
- Nathan Coye: account with Field & Little, 1855-1858 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1867 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1869 (Box 3)
- Elmer Nathan Coye: diary, 1869 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1883 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1888 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1889 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1890 (Box 3)
- Elmer Nathan Coye: diary, 1890 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1891 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1892 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1893 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1894 (Box 3)
- Lydia Laverna Holcomb: diary, 1896 (Box 3)